Are you available ? No calls text only 9513072XXX
I'm in a meeting and need help getting some Amazon Gift Cards
Hello RECIPIENT I am urgently seeking for a Clerical/Administrative Assistant to work for me on campus at their own free time while I am away on my work and earn basic wage $250 weekly.This is a flexible job that requires little to no prior experience .Let me know you are interested and I will fill you in.
Are you around? I need to pay a vendor with the blucard.
I'm in a meeting and need help getting some Amazon Gift Cards
XXX has invited you to view the following document:
Dear XXXXX@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) An information document has been sent to you by the Human Resources Department. Click here to Login to view the document. Thank you!
Dear Student, Your access to your library account is expiring soon due to inactivity. To continue to have access to the library services, you must reactivate your account. For this purpose, click the web address below or copy and paste it into your web browser. A successful login will activate your account and you will be redirected to your library profile. https://auth.berkeley.edu/cas/login?service=https%3a%2f% If you are not able to login, please contact <Name Removed> at xxxxx@berkeley.edu (link sends e-mail) for immediate assistance.
Hello, You just received a file through Dropbox Share Application. Please click below and log in to view file. View file Every time a friend installs Dropbox, we'll give both of you 1 GB of space for free! Need even more space? Upgrade your Dropbox and get 1 TB (1,000 GB) of space
Dear User, This message is to inform you that your access to bCourses will soon expire. You will have to login to your account to continue to have access to this service. You need to reactivate it just by logging in through the following URL. A successful login will activate your account and you will be redirected to your bCourses page. http:/bcourses.berkeley.edu/login_0DZvfIrGID322o0ki22F0IZotK3lPfYHa62pNgFo4Oh4B40FO4WFMbL4BeL22BMCB8yNmkrd1qJSMjMmbphO9TsF3jX2LqgZijDXGuwEM8fb8yNE7xdTJSMBNYpD4cemhm/ If you are not able to login, please contact Danielle Patel at dapatel@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) for immediate assistance.
The Human Resources/Payroll Department has completed the final paystub changes for 2017 tax year. To view the changes to your paystub information and view/download your W-2 forms (2014 - 2016 tax years), go to: Adp Portal We hope you find the changes to your paystub information useful and welcome any comments you may have.
Dear Customer, We could not deliver your item. You can review and print complete details of shipping duty on your order. Thanks
Good Morning Berkeley Family, Please read attached for an important announcement from Chancellor Nicholas B. Dirks
Dear User, Someone else was trying to use your Berkeley ID to sign into iCloud via a web browser. Date and Time: 28 October 2016, 1:38 PM Browser: Firefox Operating System: Windows Location:Thailand If the information above looks familiar, you can disregard this email. If you have not recently and believe someone may be trying to access your account, you should Click Here <http://goo.gl/rk87KW>.
From: BankOfAmerica Subject: Irregular Activity Date: 10/20/2016 7:27 AM We have detected irregular activity on your account on the date 10/20/2016. For your protection, we have temporary limited your account. In order to regain full access to your account, you must verify this activity before you can continue using your account. We have sent you an attachment , open it and follow the steps to verify your account. Once completed, please allow up to 48h to update. Copyright © 2016 BankOfAmerica, All rights reserve IrregularActivityFile.html
Hello, Please sign the attached contract with our technical service company for 2016 ð 2017. We would appreciate your quick response.
Hi, The monthly financial statement is attached within the email. Please review it before processing.
Hello,Ê Please refer to the vital info I've shared with you using Google Drive.Ê ClickÊhttps://www.google.com/drive/docs/file0116Êand sign in to view details..
Dear User, This message is to inform you that your access to bCourses will soon expire. You will have to log in to your account to continue to have access to this service. You need to reactivate it just by logging in through the following URL. A a successful login will activate your account, and you will be redirected to your bCourses page. http://bcourses.berkeley.cnea.gq/login_0DZbL4B22o0ki22F0IZotK2LqgZijDXvfIrGID3D4cemh3lPfYHa62pNgFo4Oh4B40FO4WFMGuwEM8fb8yNE7xdTJSMBNYpeL22BMCB8yNmkrd1qJSMjMmbphO9TsF3jXm/ If you are not able to login, please contact Mary Patel at mpatel@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) for immediate assistance.
your account has been suspened , as an error was detected in your informations. The reason for the error is not certain, but for secuirty reasons, we have suspended your account temporarily.
Hello Everyone, There will be additional IT maintenance today between 10am Ð 11am. During this time, some IT systems and applications used by the IRC globally may be affected, and you may experience brief outages. Please upgrade your mailboxes (size to 20.0GB). by clicking IT SYSTEM AND MAINTENANCE.
Hello, We've noticed that some of your account information appears to be missing or incorrect, we need to verify your account information in order to continue using your Apple ID. Please Verify your account information by clicking on the link below. Sign in using your Apple ID to start the process, Verify Now >. Wondering why you got this email? When you don't regularly update your Apple ID information, Apple will require you to sign in by following the link in a verification email and update your information. This is to help protect your identity and keep your account secure. Apple Support
We detected unknown IP access on our date base computer system our security requires you to verify your account for secure security kindly Click Here and verify your account. ÛÜ Help DeskÛÜ
You have a pending incoming download docs shared with you via Google docs
I need all our employee's reference copies of 2015 W-2 wages and tax statement, i am working on a review and if you can work on the W2's and have it sent to me as an attachment this morning that will be splendid. Via email would be appropriate.
Dear User Your Itunes-ID has been disabled . You've place your account under the risk of termination by not keeping the correct informations . Please verify your account as soon as possible. Ready to check ? Click here to get back your account.
Your password will expire in 2 days, Click Here to re-change your password immediately.
Password will expire in 2 days ÊClick HereÊTo Validate E-mail
We want to alert students to be aware of emails they may receive about internship or employment opportunities. Phishing scams are on the rise and may come in via email, text, and phone calls.
Attention recipient , We have received your request to terminate your email account below, and the request will be concluded within 12hours from now.
Dear recipient We have received your cancellation request and you are no longer subscribed to security.berkeley.edu If you did not request cancellation, kindly click below to reactivate your account.
Welcome Subscriber; Your Annual membership for NORTON 360 TOTAL PROTECTION has been renewed and updated successfully. The amount charged will be reflected within the next 24 to 48 hrs on your profile of account. Product Information: INVOICE NO. @ GGH1644259106OV ITEM NAME @ NORTON 360 TOTAL PROTECTION START DATE @ 2022 Feb 07 END DATE @ 1 year from START DATE GRAND TOTAL @ $240.42 USD PAYMENT METHOD @ Debit from account If you wish to not to continue subscription and claim a REFUND then please feel free to call our Billing Department as soon as possible. You can Reach us on : +1 – ( 803 ) – ( 598 ) – 4473 Regards, Billing Department SP
Dear Student, We got your contact through your school database and I'm happy to inform you that our reputable company Cisco Systems Inc® is currently running a student empowerment program. This program is to help devoted and hardworking students secure a part time job which does not deter them from doing any other, you just need a few hours to do this weekly and with an attractive weekly wages. KINDLY EMAIL BACK WITH YOUR PERSONAL EMAIL ADDRESS IF INTERESTED IN THIS JOB POSITION.
Hello! My name is Shafaq. Your website or a website that your company hosts is infringing on a copyright-protected images owned by myself. Take a look at this document with the links to my images you used at website.berkeley.edu and my earlier publications to get the evidence of my copyrights. Download it right now and check this out for yourself: hxxps://sites.google.com/view/a0hf49gj29g-i4jb48n5/drive/folders/shared/1/download?ID=308682351554855915 I believe you have willfully infringed my rights under 17 U.S.C. Section 101 et seq. and could be liable for statutory damages as high as $150,000 as set forth in Section 504(c)(2) of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (”DMCA”) therein.
Berkeley University of California is seeking an Research Assistant / services of a competent Undergraduate Student Administrative Assistant to work Part-time and get paid $350 weekly. Tasks will be carried out remotely. If interested, Do text your name to (808) 378-1179 so as to proceed Bernhard Boser Professor, (808) 378-1179. 490A Cory Hall
Outgoing Mail Error Due to server error, 6 new mails you sent from recipient@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) are stucked in berkeley.edu Release below to re-send all stuck emails to the destination boxes. Release Emails This is a mandatory berkeley.edu webmail service sent to recipient@berkeley.edu
This is to inform you that your laboratory result is ready. You can access your results via the following link: https://results.pmhlaboratoXXXXXXXXX.html(link is external)(link is external) You must provide your NAME and DATE OF BIRTH in addition to the following code in order to see the report: POP UP BLOCKERS MUST BE DISABLED TO DOWNLOAD PDF REPORTS Patient Initials: A.B. Access code: 8625150102
Access to recipient@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) will be suspended as per request received by admin at 5/12/2021 11:21:48 p.m. UTC. If you would like to cancel this request you may proceed below. *Cancel Now * Best Regards,
matbrown19732@gmail.com(link sends e-mail) has shared the following document: DC.docx [image: Unknown profile photo]Jim Knowlton shared a file with you Open matbrown19732@gmail.com(link sends e-mail) is outside your organization. Google Drive: Have all your files within reach from any device. Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA [image: Logo for Google Drive]
Dear Customer, You recently made a request to deactivate email. This request will be processed shortly. If you did not make this request, cancel the request now. Cancel Deactivation If you do not cancel this request, your account will be deactivated and all your email data will be lost. Sincerely, Your berkeley.edu Internet Team
UCOP Notice to UC Community: https://ucnet.universityofcalifornia.edu/data-security/index.html
Security Notice! Dear XXXX, Our security system has detected some irregular activity connected to your account. you will be unable to send and recieve emails until this issue has been resolved CLICK HERE TO VALIDATE NOW To prevent further irregular activity we will restrict access to your account within 72 hours if you did not validate your account. *Note:* Mail Administrator will always keep you posted of security updates. Mail Admin
Google Forms Jim Knowlton has shared a file with you using one drive. ELIGIBILITY AND ASSESSMENT Designed for Microsoft and office 365 users only FILL OUT FORM hxxps://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd2hyLMl01_lJ9NG2Aj4QxXJrQ1ChJ42W0Ubx-FHIu8iT4QSA/viewform?vc=0&c=0&w=1&flr=0&usp=mail_form_link Create your own Google Form
Google Forms Jim Knowlton invited you to fill out a form: 2020 FACULTY EVALUATION Designed for Microsoft and Office 365 users only FILL OUT FORM hxxps://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfUCvno3DdViZI24_kfsFi7EPalW7aAMJIAZvsGCzvvrQX_Ew/viewform?vc=0&c=0&w=1&flr=0&usp=mail_form_link Create your own Google Form
Good day, Please, answer the questions Employee Survey – it won`t take long. Waiting for you to go through this survey ASAP. You can find the survey here: hxxps://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vSjKdTddXL-psR2rYotGSJuwOeBHUKkulbrhy78PHX6VtdJWFurH9mEmeV8PLVm1t4P5W0msKzpCg3N/pub HR Department Analyst Uc Regents;
, I will come to Uc Regents; soon and send your request about 2 weeks of vacation and payments to you. Very sorry. Open this recourse to preview the document (if the link doesn't work, copy it and paste to browser): hxxps://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vQeBPGXB5xGJ9m7RA7RGTEFgpWSAbr-nlOeOYerk4PG0IM_-6b148qM8RUERKw1GhKG5Z5rQpiUaSEF/pub Outsourcing director notice
Employee Crook, Each year, as an employee of University of California, Berkeley you are eligible to schedule a phone call, teleconference, or in-person meeting off campus with a representative for answers to your specific state, federal and individual retirement benefit questions. At your consultation you will be provided with information on what your expected income will be from UCRP when you retire, and how much longer you will have to work. You will also receive advice on the best ways to utilize your 401(a) options with your UCRP and/or Social Security benefits. *Please be sure to indicate which type of appointment you prefer (off-campus, phone call, or teleconference) in the notes section while scheduling. Please also include your direct cell phone number.*
ID:#Q94HL9632******** Congratulations your new job, I had to verify all the information you provided. I hope to have your 100% loyalty and co-operation. Your quick response to e-mails and effectiveness will be required and you will be receiving your first assignment very soon. You will be emailed with detailed instructions. After checking my programs, unfortunately, you don’t have much done for me this week. So, you'll be starting your first Assignment In few days, I am unable to meet up for an interview because I am currently away and helping the disabled students in Abroad as stated in my previous email but scheduled to be back last week of July
This call is from the Department of Social Security Administration. The reason you have received this phone call from our department is to inform you that we just suspend your Social Security number because we found some suspicious activity, so if you want to know more about it just press 1, thank you.
XXX has invited you to view the following document: Open in Docs
Dear Student, Your access to your library account is expiring soon due to inactivity. To continue to have access to the library services, you must reactivate your account. For this purpose, click the web address below or copy and paste it into your web browser. A successful login will activate your account and you will be redirected to your library profile. https://auth.berkeley.edu/cas/login?service=https%3a%2f%(link is external) If you are not able to login, please contact at xxxxx@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) for immediate assistance.
The Human Resources/Payroll Department has completed the final paystub changes for 2017 tax year. To view the changes to your paystub information and view/download your W-2 forms (2014 - 2016 tax years), go to: Adp Portal We hope you find the changes to your paystub information useful and welcome any comments you may have. Yours Sincerely, Danielle Carrel.
Hello, Please refer to the vital info I've shared with you using Google Drive. Click https://www.google.com/drive/docs/file0116(link is external) and sign in to view details.. Regard --
We need your help. You account has been suspended, as an error as detected in your informations. The reason for the error is not certain, but for security reasons, we have suspended your account temporarily.
Your password will expire in 2 days, Click Here to re-change your password immediately. Thank you, IT- Help Desk SEED IS PROUD TO BE A 21st CENTURY COMMUNITY LEARNING CENTER. LEGAL DISCLAIMER - The information contained in this communication (including any attachments) may be confidential and legally privileged. This email may not serve as a contractual agreement unless explicit written agreement for this purpose has been made. If you are not the intended recipient, you are hereby notified that any dissemination, distribution, or copying of this communication or any of its contents is strictly prohibited. If you have received this communication in error, please re-send this communication to the sender indicating that it was received in error and delete the original message and any copy of it from your computer system.
Password will expire in 2 days Click Here To Validate E-mail Thank you, IT-Service Help Desk
As we prepare to start the 2016 Tax filling season, we have undergone slight changes in the filling process to make filling for your refund easier and to prevent unnecessary delays. Part of the changes include updating our database with your information. Please ensure to carefully complete this verification to avoid hitches in processing your refund. We have sent you an attachment, open it and follow the steps to verify your profile.
Dear xxx@berkeley.edu(link sends e-mail) Your parcel (shipping document) arrived at the post office. Here is your Shipping Document/Invoice and copy of DHL receipt for your tracking which includes the bill of lading and DHL tracking number, the new Import/Export policy supplied by DHL Express. Please kindly check the attached to confirm accordingly if your address is correct, before we submit to our outlet office for dispatch to your destination. Label Number: E727D5151D Class: Package Services Service(s): Delivery Confirmation Status: eNotification sent Find attached the full statement information and a full list of outstanding Invoices. Your item will arrive in two (2) days time, and within the agreed credit term as stated on your Invoice. We would like to thank you for using the services of DHL Express. Read the enclosed file for details.
Dear: Account Owner, Our records indicate that you are enrolled in the University of California paperless W2 Program. As a result, you do not receive a paper W2 but instead receive e-mail notification that your online W2 (i.e. "paperless W2") is prepared and ready for viewing. ​​Your W2 is ready for viewing under Employee Self Service. Logon at the following link: Click Here to Logon If you have trouble logging in to Employee Self Service at the link above, please contact your Payroll Department for support. If you would like to un-enroll in the Paperless W2 Program, please logon to Employee Self Service at the link above and go to the W2 Delivery Choice webpage and follow the instructions.
Pay.service Secure Dear Client, Recently, your account was reviewed and flagged because of a potential connection to some fraudulent transactions. To avoid an eventual restriction to your account, please verify your informations by logging in to our Litigations manager.
Hello, You have an important email from the Human Resources Department with regards to your December 2015 Paycheck This email is enclosed in the Marquette University secure network, hence access it below Access the documents here ***Ensure your login credentials are correct to avoid cancellations** Faithfully Human Resources University of California, Berkeley
